Here's a list of orders in the last month,
هذه مجموعة من الأوامر في الشهر الأخير،
assuming it's currently January 2017.
بافتراض أننا في يناير 2017.
I'm using mode to run these queries,
أستخدم وضعًا لتشغيل هذه الاستعلامات،
which tells me that there are 463 rows in my result set.
مما يخبرني بوجود 463 صفًا في مجموعة النتائج.
Still, you'll need to learn to count in SQL,
ما زلت تحتاج لتعلم العدّ في SQL،
because you can use it to count in
حتى يمكنك استخدامه للعد
a much more fine-grained way than simply counting all the rows in a result set.
بطريقة جيدة وسلسة بدلاً من عد جميع الصفوف في مجموعة النتائج.
We can do this by modifying our SELECT statement to use a COUNT function.
يمكننا فعل ذلك عن طريق تعديل عبارة SELECT لاستخدام وظيفة COUNT.
You can see that this returns a single row of output in a single column,
يمكنك رؤية أن ذلك يُرجع صفًا واحدًا من المخرجات في عمود واحد،
and the value is exactly the same as the row count we saw before.
والقيمة هي نفسها مثل عدد الصفوف الذي رأيناه من قبل.
Let's give that column an alias,
لنعطي هذا العمود اسمًا مستعارًا،
so that it's a little easier to read.
ليكون سهل القراءة.
Okay, much better. So, how does this work?
حسنًا، أفضل بكثير. إذًا كيف يعمل ذلك؟
The COUNT function is returning a count of all the rows that contain some non-null data.
تقوم وظيفة COUNT بإرجاع عدد كل الصفوف التي تحتوي على بعض البيانات التي ليست خالية.
It's very unusual to have a row that is entirely null.
على غير المعتاد أن يكون صفًا كاملاً خاليًا.
So, the result produced by a
لذا، يتم إنتاج النتيجة بواسطة
COUNT(*) is typically equal to the number of rows in the table.
COUNT(*) وهو مساوي لعدد الصفوف في الجدول.